Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ongoing Career, 1993; XVII.
  - Events, 4.
    - American Disability Act (ADA) meeting with British Embassy, Washington, DC, July 21, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 11)
    - American Bar Association (ABA) convention, New Orleans, LA, August 4-10, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 12)
    - William Hague, lunch, Washington, DC, September 12, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 13)
    - The Brookings Institute, seminar, Washington, DC, September 19, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 14)
    - Betty Montgomery, Campaign for Attorney General, Columbus, OH, September 26, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 15)
    - Trinity University, lecture, San Antonio, TX, September 29, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 16)
    - PBS "This Is America" interview with Dennis Wholey, Washington, DC, October 7, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 17)
    - Ray Gruender campaign for prosecutor, St. Louis, MO, October 12, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 18)
    - National Center for State Courts, Williamsburg, VA, October 17-18, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 19)
    - Dennis Vacco, Campaign for Attorney General, Rochester, NY, October 18-19, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 20)
    - Dixon University Center, dedication Harrisburg, PA, October 20, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 21)
    - Attorneys General Forum, Hastings Law School, San Francisco, CA, October 22, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 22)
    - Tom Ridge Gubernatorial Campaign endorsement, Pittsburgh, PA, October 24, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 23)
    - Greenwood for Congress campaign, Doylestown, PA, October 24, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 24)
    - "Mitchells in the Morning" interview, Washington, DC, October 31, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 25)
    - National Strategy Forum, Cantigny Conference Series, Chicago, IL, November 3-4, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 26)
    - McLean Clergy Association, keynote address, McLean, VA, November 6, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 27)
    - Council for Court Excellence, Washington, DC, "Limits to Free Speech," public forum, November 22, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Society 96th Annual Dinner, New York, NY, December 10, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 29)
    - Reagan Administration Christmas lunch, Washington, DC, December 15, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 30)
    - Inkatha Freedom Party (IFP), meeting, guest speaker Dr. Ruth Rabinowitz, December 15, 1994 (Box 999, Folder 31)
    - Tom Ridge Gubernatorial Inauguration, Harrisburg, PA, January 17, 1995 (Box 999, Folder 32)
    - "What to Do About Violent Crime?," Muskingham College, New Concord, OH, January 24, 1995 (Box 999, Folder 33)
    - "Is Crime Killing America," University of Alabama, Tuscaloosa, AL:, January 30, 1995 (Box 999, Folder 34)
    - "Good Morning America" interview, Washington, DC, February 6, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 1)
    - Washington Legal Foundation (WLF), Supreme Court Media Briefing, M.J. Murdock Center, Washington, DC, February 7, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 2)
    - Renaissance Weekend XIX, Hilton Head, SC, February 16-20, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 3)
    - Mr. & Mrs. George Soros, dinner reception, Cassese & Goldstone, NY, February 23, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 4)
    - Harry S. Truman Scholarship Foundation, Selection of Truman Scholars, Washington, DC, February 24, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 5)
    - International Law Institute, Tom Dine luncheon, Washington, DC, March 1, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Chronicle interview regarding UN reform, Washington, DC, March 6, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 7)
    - The Federalist Society, University of Maryland School of Law, Baltimore, MD, March 9, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 8)
    - Cumberland School of Law, Birmingham, AL, March 14, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 9)
    - "Is Crime Killing America," Kent State University, Canton, OH, March 15, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 10)
    - "Sustaining the Central City into the Twenty-first Century: Involving the Private Sector and the Local Community," roundtable discussion and seminar, Pittsburgh, PA, March 17, 1995, May 19, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 11)
    - Turner Publishing interview with James Holtje regarding UN reform, Washington, DC, March 22, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 12)
    - "Crime and Violence in America," Illinois Benedictine College, Lisle, IL, March 23, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 13)
    - "Challenges to the American Legal System," Mississippi Law Day Banquet, Jackson, MS, March 24, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 14)
    - Lord Windelson, meeting, Washington DC, March 27, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 15)
    - Tulane University Lecture Series, New Orleans, LA, April 3, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 16)
    - "Partnerships in Science and Technology: New Paths to Prosperity," The Franklin Area Chamber of Commerce Annual Dinner Meeting, Franklin, PA, April 4, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 17)
    - "Attorney's Lunch" with Larry King, Washington, DC, April 6, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 18)
    - The Federalist Society, Villanova University, Villanova, PA, April 6, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 19)
    - Yale Political Union, The Conservative Forum at Yale University, New Haven, CT, April 11, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 20)
    - Debate with Milton Grimes, University of Nevada, Las Vegas, NV, April 13, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 21)
    - United Nations, Peacekeeping and Lessons for American Policy, Second Conference, Aspen Institute, St. Croix, U.S. Virgin Islands, April 17 -22, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 22)
    - Mellon Trust 1995 Client Conference, Turnberry Isle Resort and Club, Aventura, FL, April 23-24, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 23)
    - United Nation Association (UNA), luncheon, New York, NY, April 29, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 24)
    - 14th Policy Exchange Foundation Conference, Phoenix, AZ, May 4-5, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 25)
    - Defiance College Commencement Ceremonies, speaker, Defiance, OH, May 7, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 26)
    - National Institute of Justice Conference Seminar, Washington, DC, May 15, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 27)
    - National Leadership Summit of the American Legislative Exchange Council (ALEC), Richmond, VA, May 18-21, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 28)
    - Seminar on Federal Budget Reductions and the Impact on the State of Pennsylvania, Institute of Politics, University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA, May 19, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 29)
    - International Republican Institute, Tenley Center, Washington, DC, May 23, 1995 (Box 1000, Folder 30)
    - Pepperdine University, Los Angeles, CA, June 8, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 1)
    - California District Attorneys Association, Summer Conference, South Lake Tahoe, NV, June 27, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut Republican Junior Internship Program, Hartford, CT, July 11, 1985, July 25, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 3)
    - "Florida On-Line," radio show interview with the Madison Institute, Washington, DC, July 12, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 4)
    - WESA Radio Morning Show, phone interview celebrating the shows birthday, Washington, DC, July 13, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 5)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) Fifth Anniversary Celebration, Washington, DC, July 25, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 6)
    - American Bar Association (ABA) Justice Section Annual Meeting, program panelist, Washington, DC, August 4-6, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 7)
    - Meeting with Robert Rafferty of West Virginia Wesleyan College regarding career choices, Washington, DC, August 14, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 8)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Shen Fu-hsiung, dinner, Washington, DC, August 15, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 9)
    - Public Law Seminar, Law 426, George Washington University Law School, Washington, DC, Fall, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 10)
    - Official Portrait Presentation of The Honorable Dick Thornburgh, Seventy-Sixth Attorney General of the United States, Washington, D.C, September 28, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 11)
    - Republican Disability Coalition, Inaugural Reception, Washington, DC, October 10, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 12)
    - National Organization on Disability (NOD), Reception of Mike Deland, Chairman NOD, Washington, DC, October 11, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 13)
    - American Leadership Conference, Session III, Washington, DC, October 17, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 14)
    - Community Awareness Reception Fundraiser, The Women's Center and Shelter, Pittsburgh, PA, October 18, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 15)
    - Overseas Development Council (ODO), Luncheon, Washington, DC, October 30, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 16)
    - Leadership Lake County, Inc. and City Club of Cleveland Forum Series, Wickliffe, OH, November 15, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 17)
    - "An Evening with Larry King and Friends," fundraiser for Larry King Cardiac Foundation, Washington, DC, December 1, 1995 (Box 1001, Folder 18)
    - Omicron Delta Kappa, 39th Biennial Convention, West Lafayette, IN, March 23, 1996 (Box 1001, Folder 19)
    - "Roles of Responsibilities of the Secretary-General of the United States," statement regarding UN reform, Washington, DC, November 14, 1996 (Box 1001, Folder 20)
    - Founder's Day Symposium on occasion of Gift of Papers of Dick Thornburgh to University of Pittsburgh, February 27, 1998 (Box 1001, Folder 21)
    - Three Mile Island Panel Discussion and Reception, University of Pittsburgh, March 26, 1999 (Box 1001, Folder 22)
    - President Bush Awards medal to ADA advocates Dick and Ginny Thornburgh, Houston, Texas; AND Free Library of Philadelphia reception and archival exhibit, February 14,2000, November 13, 2000 (Box 1001, Folder 23)
    - "Crisis Management" Lecture, University of Pittsburgh, Paul Critchlow lecturer, November 30, 2000 (Box 1001, Folder 24)
    - George H.W.Bush Oral History Project Interview, including final edited transcript, Charlottesville, VA., October 23-24, 2001 (Box 1001, Folder 25)
    - Lincoln Day Event Honoring Dick Thornburgh, Union League, Philadelphia, PA, February 12, 2003 (Box 1001, Folder 26)
    - Henry B. Betts Award to Dick and Ginny Thornburgh, March 4, 2003 (Box 1001, Folder 27)
    - Thornburgh-Scranton 25th anniversary symposium, Hershey, PA, November 19, 2003 (Box 1001, Folder 28)
    - Thornburgh-Scranton 25th Anniversary Reunion, November 19, 2003 (Box 1001, Folder 29)
    - Three Mile Island Symposium, sponsored by Smithsonian, Washington, D.C., March 28, 2004 (Box 1001, Folder 30)
    - Events By Year, 1993-2004 (Box 1002, Folder 1-12)
    - K&L Schedules, 1994-2001 (Box 1002, Folder 13)
    - New Material Added, December 2014
      - Council on Foreign Relations, 'Chinese 'Economic Miracle', Washington, September 14, 1994 (Box 1036, Folder A)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, Washington: US - UN Relations, March 2, 2000 (Box 1036, Folder 1)
      - Honoring F. Eugene Dixon, Jr. Retirement from State Board of High Education Board, Harrisburg, July 12, 2000 (Box 1036, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, Washington- UN in 21st Century, October 2, 2000 (Box 1036, Folder 3)
      - Bush-Cheney Transition Advisory Committee re DOJ, January 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 4)
      - National Assoc. of Asst. US Attorneys Dinner, February 7, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 5)
      - CNN Late Edition/Wolf Blitzer, Gary Condit legal problems, September 2, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 6)
      - Anti-Corruption Conference sponsored by World Bank, Washington, September 13, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 7)
      - National Day of Prayer and Remembrance, Washington, September 14, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 8)
      - All Attorney Dinner at Women's National Democratic Club, Washington, September 24, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 9)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: War on Terrorism event (Thornburgh moderated), Washington, October 19, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 10)
      - Corporate Legal Times Roundtable: Trends in New Regulations, November 12, 2001 (Box 1036, Folder 11)
      - National Assoc. Subrogation Professionals, Reno (Thornburgh remarks), February 2002 (Box 1036, Folder 11a)
      - 3rd Conference of International Investigators hosted by World Bank, Washington (T. speaker), March 7-8, 2002 (Box 1036, Folder 12)
      - OGC University, conference sponsored by Governor's Office of General Counsel, Hershey PA, July 11, 2002 (Box 1036, Folder 13)
      - Brookings with NAFSA: Seminar "Political Economic Challenges in Global Environment, Washington, March 17, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 14)
      - Georgetown Univ. Public Policy Institute & Moscow School of Political Studies Seminar on American Federalism, Washington, March 18, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 15)
      - Brooklings Inst. & Sloan School of Management MIT Field Trip for Sloan Fellows, Washington, March 24, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 16)
      - Univ. of Pgh SIS: Student presentations re Nuclear Power & Crisis Management, Pittsburgh, March 26, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 17)
      - Dick Thornburgh Archival Collection Reception, Pittsburgh, April 2, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 18)
      - Jay Waldman Remembrance Service, Bala Cynwyd, PA, June 2, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 19)
      - National Foundation for Teaching Entrepreneurship, June 11, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 20)
      - Thornburgh-Scranton Administration 25th Anniversary Celebration, Hershey, November 19, 2003 (Box 1036, Folder 21)
      - Georgetown Univ. Law Center Annual Corporate Counsel Institute: Homeland Security, March 12, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 22)
      - Smithsonian Panel Discussion: Three Mile Island, looking back after 25 years, Washington (video available), March 28, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 23)
      - United States District Court Memorial service Honoring Jay Waldman (Transcript of all remarks), Philadelphia, May 7, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 24)
      - Council on Foreign Relations re Hong Kong, Washington, May 19, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 25)
      - Bush-Cheney '04 Patriot Act Press Conference, Washington, June 2, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 26)
      - Reception for Tom Corbett, Republican Candidate for PA Attorney General, September 21, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 27)
      - Woodstock Theological Center/Georgetown Univ. Law Center, "A Crisis in Corporate Governance" Georgetown, October 12, 2004 (Box 1036, Folder 28)
      - K&L Summer Associates: "Report of the CBS Investigation of "60 Minutes Wednesday", Washington, June 17, 2005 (Box 1036, Folder 29)
      - Dedication of William R. Eleazer Barrier-free Courtroom, Gulfport, FL, September 16, 2005 (Box 1036, Folder 30)
      - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh "Defining US Relationship with UN in 21st Century, September 28, 2005 (Box 1036, Folder 31)
      - Events by year, 2005 (Box 1036, Folder 32)
      - Events by year, 2006 (Box 1036, Folder 33)
      - University of Pittsburgh Honors Convocation: "Education Goals University of Pittsburgh", February 24, 2006 (Box 1036, Folder 34)
      - Dick Thornburgh Legacy Project Event, Pittsburgh, March 23, 2006 (Box 1036, Folder 35)
      - Radisson Seven Seas Cruise to Middle East, Thornburgh a "Capital Speaker", April 6-14, 2006 (Box 1036, Folder 36)
      - Gauer Lecture in Law & Public Policy, Transcript with Thornburgh annotations, September 21, 2006 (Box 1036, Folder 37)
      - Events by year, 2007 (Box 1036, Folder 38)
      - University Dedicates Dick Thornburgh Room in Hillman Library & Establishes Forum for Law & Public Policy, April 5, 2007 (Box 1036, Folder 39)
      - Dedication of Jay Waldman Seminar Room and Thornburgh Forum for Law & Public Policy, November 27, 2007 (Box 1036, Folder 40)
      - Events by year, 2008 (Box 1036, Folder 41)
      - Events by year, 2009 (Box 1036, Folder 42)
      - Events by year, 2010 (Box 1036, Folder 43)
      - Albany Law Symposium on Public Executive Records in the 21st Century, Albany, May 20-21, 2010 (Box 1036, Folder 44)
      - Program on "Atticus Finch and Ethics", Fort Worth, Texas, June 10, 2010 (Box 1036, Folder 45)
      - PCN Oral History Interview, Wicklow, Ligonier, PA, August 3, 2011 (Box 1036, Folder 46)
      - Nuclear Power Symposium, DT Forum, Pittsburgh, PA, March 27-28, 2012 (Box 1036, Folder 47)
      - Dick Thornburgh's 80th Birthday Celebration, Pittsburgh, PA, July 15, 2012 (Box 1036, Folder 48)
      - American Experience Lecture, University of Pgh, 2012 Presidential Election, Pittsburgh, PA, October 18, 2012 (Box 1036, Folder 49)
      - Events by year, 2012 (Box 1036, Folder 50)
      - Annual Calendars, 1993-2011 (Box 1038, Folder 1-19)
      - Annual Phone Logs, 2004-2007 (Box 1038, Folder 20)
    - New Material Added, August 2018
      - Oxford Union Debate vs. Sir Patrick Mahew, London, January 30, 1992 (Box 1055, Folder 1)
      - Major League Baseball Interview, June 7, 1993 (Box 1055, Folder 2)
      - New Jersey Bar Association Meeting: Speech: "Civil Justice Reform", May 21, 1994 (Box 1055, Folder 3)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting Panel Evaluator: "Crime, Justice, and Society", August 2, 1994 (Box 1055, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Seminar (K&L), Miami, November 17, 1994 (Box 1055, Folder 5)
      - Trusteeship of Dole Foundation for Employment of People with Disabilities, March 1994-November 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 6)
      - Partnerships in Science and Technology: State-Federal Partnership Task Force, December 7, 1994 (Box 1055, Folder 7)
      - Dept. of Commerce Subcommittee: Institute of Standard and Technology: statement Arati Prabhakar, March 15, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 8)
      - International Republican Institute: Guatemala (cancelled), May 4, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 9)
      - Science/Technology Task Force Meeting, May 26, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 10)
      - New Jersey Commission on Science & Technology Speech, July 17, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 11)
      - George Washington University Law School Course: "Creating and Maintaining Integrity in Governmental Organizations", Fall 1995 Semester (Box 1055, Folder 12)
      - Congressman Robert Walker, House Science Committee Chair event, August 22, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Coalition for Technology Partnerships & Science Technology working group, remarks, August 16, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 14)
      - Luther College remarks "Issues in Affirmative Action", September 7, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 15)
      - Federalist Society: "From O.J. to Tort Tax: Continuing Battle over Legal Reform", September 12, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 16)
      - Mass. Coalition of Citizens with Disabilities: "The ADA Five Years Later", September 15, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 17)
      - Penn State University: "Crime and Violence in America", September 19, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 18)
      - State Legislative Science & Technology Conf. Harvard University: "Remarks", September 21, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 19)
      - Debate Ralph Nader/Thornburgh on Product Liability Reform, Williams College, September 23, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 20)
      - University of Tennessee Remarks: "Legal Reform in America", October 3,1995 (Box 1055, Folder 21)
      - Ohio Attorneys General Enforcement Conference: Presentation, October 5, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 22)
      - Citizens for Civil Justice Reform Radio Interviews "Tort Reform", October 10, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 23)
      - Seattle Leadership Conference, Remarks: " Economic growth, more jobs, better quality of life", October 14, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 24)
      - Central Michigan University; Remarks: "Crime and Violence in America", October 16, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 25)
      - Frederick Community College, MD: Remarks: "Crime and Violence in America", October 23, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 26)
      - National Center for State Courts, Dinner honoring Chief Justice of US William H. Rehnquist; Supreme Court, October 22, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 27)
      - National Assc. Of Police Organizations; TOP COPS AWARDS CEREMONY, October 25, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 28)
      - International Law Institute, Moscow; Commercial Law Judicial Training, October 24-26, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 29)
      - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society: Notes: "Current Issues in Scientific Research", November 1, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 30)
      - Americans for Lawsuit Reform: Briefing: "Lawsuit Abuse: The Magnitude of the Problem", November 3, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 31)
      - Yale Center for International & Area Studies; Speech "Business Crime Goes International", November 4, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 32)
      - Rotary International, W. VA; Speech Notes: "The United Nations at Fifty: The Challenge of Change", November 10, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 33)
      - Smithsonian Associates program; Speech "Coping With Transnational Crime", November 14, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 34)
      - WHJJ Radio, "Rudy Cheeks/John Hackett show: Notes: Civil Justice Reform, November 17, 1995 (Box 1055, Folder 35)
      - Economic Development Comm, Florida, "What's Ahead in Politics", January 26, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 36)
      - Union Club of Boston: Remarks "An Inside View of Washington Today", January 30, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 37)
      - Hong Kong Economic & Trade Office event: Remarks "Rule of Law Run-up and Beyond 1997", January 31, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 38)
      - Reception National Governors' Association honoring South African Ambassador Franklin Sonn, February 3, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 39)
      - American University Federalist Society; Remarks "Crime and the Criminal Justice System", Februrary 20, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 40)
      - OU (Oklahoma University) Federalist Society; Remarks "From O.J. to the Tort Tax: The Continuing Battle Over Legal Reform", March 21, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 41)
      - Young Republican National Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C.; Remarks: Spirited Contests in 1996 Primary, February 22, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 42)
      - Luncheon San Diego County; Topic Juvenile Delinquency Prevention Needs, March 1, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 43)
      - Omicron Delta Kappa Convention, National Leadership Honor Society, Purdue University, West Lafayette, Ind: Remarks "An American Century…The Challenge of Leadership", March 23, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 44)
      - Messiah College Susquehanna Valley Lyceum; Remarks "Crime and Justice in America", March 29, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 45)
      - Meeting Muhlenberg College "College of Asian and Western Learning, Dr. Dorothy Guyot, April 1, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 46)
      - CNN Guest Taping: "Burden of Proof" Prime Time Special, Multiple topics: Unabomber, Charles Keating convictions, Whitewater, and others (Box 1055, Folder 47)
      - "CBS This Morning": Unabomber and other topics, April 6, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 48)
      - Hanover College Convocation, Hanover, IN: Remarks "Crime and Criminal Justice System", April 8, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 49)
      - "The Accent Program at University of Florida ": Debate with Michael Dukakis re Primary Season, April 12, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 50)
      - Dukakis Debate-continued, April 16, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 51)
      - Kansas City Public Library "Kickoff for National Library Week"; Remarks " Which Issues Will Define Campaign '96?", April 18, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 52)
      - Meeting of M.J. Murdock Charitable Trust Board at Washington Legal Foundation; Talking points, April 29, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 53)
      - Fresno, CA, Trade Club Recognition Dinner: Speech "Rights and Responsibilities in a Free Society", May 4,1996 (Box 1055, Folder 54)
      - Republican Committee of Chester County Four Star Reception: Thornburgh Guest of Honor, May 15, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 55)
      - 1996 Truman Scholars Leadership Week Program: Speech "Rights and Responsibilies the Challenge of Leadership in a Free Society", May 31, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 56)
      - Fundraising Event: PA State Senator D. Michael Fisher, York, PA., June 4, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 57)
      - University of Alabama The Great Debate: Benjamin Hooks vs. Richard Thornburgh; Remarks "Crime and Justice in America", June 20, 1996 (Box 1055, Folder 58)
      - Urban Institute: Policy Advisory Board Meeting, July 10, 1996 (Box 1056, Folder 1)
      - Keystone State Games, August 2, 1996 (Box 1056, Folder 2)
      - "THIS IS AMERICA with DENNIS WHOLEY", August 7, 1996 (Box 1056, Folder 3)
      - Discussion with Chinese Prosecutors Delegation, August 28, 1996 (Box 1056, Folder 4)